{
    "subject": "resource/Spanish_West_Indies",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Santo_Domingo",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Spanish West Indies is Santo Domingo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8628683090209961,
            "question": "What is the capital of Spanish West Indies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7688030004501343,
            "question": "What is the history of Santo Domingo as a capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6664858460426331,
            "question": "Where is Santo Domingo located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5462329983711243,
            "question": "Is Santo Domingo a country or a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46625104546546936,
            "question": "What are some major landmarks in Santo Domingo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40369656682014465,
            "question": "What was the name of the territory that included Spanish West Indies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.242963045835495,
            "question": "When did Spanish West Indies become a territory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.236359104514122,
            "question": "How would you describe the climate in Santo Domingo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22018976509571075,
            "question": "Are there any cultural events or festivals celebrated in Santo Domingo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19440647959709167,
            "question": "What language is primarily spoken in Santo Domingo?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Spanish West Indies is Santo Domingo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8918_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any cultural events or festivals celebrated in Santo Domingo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8918_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the climate in Santo Domingo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8918_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Spanish West Indies become a territory?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8918_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8918_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8918_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8918_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8918_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8918_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8918_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8918_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8918_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8918_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8918_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the triple \"The capital of Spanish West Indies is Santo Domingo\". Specifically, document 1.txt states that Santo Domingo was founded by Bartholomew Columbus as the first seat of the Spanish colonial rule in the New World."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Santo Domingo being the capital of the Dominican Republic, which supports the statement that \"The capital of Spanish West Indies is Santo Domingo,\" considering historical context where the Spanish West Indies referred to their colonial territories in the Caribbean."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}